Miss Parawee Withayasupanan

18 Bradbourne Drive, Carine, WA 6020 0420287798 parawee.with@gmail.com

A recent graduate from a Master of Finance with strong financial skills, including in investment analysis. High-level data analysis skills from prior actuarial training and employment. Outstanding academic achievement. Placed on the Dean's Honour Roll. Practiced time management and multi-tasking skills by maintaining part-time employment while studying. Experience working in customer service. Enthusiastic about the position.

Association

Society of Actuaries' exams: P, FM, MLC, MFE, C, VEE Economics, VEE Corporate Finance, VEE Applied Statistics, FAP Module 1-8 (Equivalent to part I and part II from Institute of Actuaries)

Skills

Language: English (Fluent), Thai (Native)

Microsoft office: Excel including VBA (Advanced), Word, PowerPoint, Outlook Other Software: Prophet (Advanced), SQL (Intermediate), R (Intermediate)

Qualification

2017-2018: Master of Finance, University of Tasmania, Australia (6.80/7.00 GPA)

2014-2015: Bachelor of Actuarial Science, Curtin University, Australia (84.75/100 CWA)

2012-2015: Bachelor of Actuarial Science, Mahidol University, Thailand (3.98/4.00 GPA)

Work experience

Mar 2018-Aug 2018: Waitress, All Thai Restaurant, Tasmania, Australia

- Presented menus to customers, answered questions about menu items, and made recommendations
- Provided friendly service with attention to detail to assure customers' satisfaction
- Provided service with telephone orders/inquiries and operated a payment terminal

Dec 2017-Feb 2018: Corporate Intern, Financial Services, University of Tasmania, Australia

- Updated internal telephone data to current usage of the university's staff
- Analysed telephone usage and reviewed its reasonableness to apply telephone services with cost efficiency

- Reported telephone usage summary
- Created an automated Excel worksheet to assist with the telephony data processing

Jan 2016-Feb 2017: Actuary, International Actuarial Department, Muang Thai Life Assurance, Thailand

- Launched insurance products for partner companies in Cambodia and Laos
 - o Pricing/Reserving/Filing/IT using Prophet and AS400
- Entered/updated insurance product data into the system
- Prepared policy contracts and terms and conditions in English for Cambodian translation
- Negotiated insurance contract agreements with reinsurers
- Gave a pricing presentation to the Director General of the Central Bank of Myanmar

Apr 2014-May 2014: Actuarial intern, Product Development Department, Thai Samsung Life Insurance, Thailand

- Practiced product design with different features
- Priced insurance products using Excel
- Conducted a competitor comparison analysis

Referees

- 1. Mr Tim Millbank, University of Tasmania (Corporate Internship Project Officer) tim.millbank@utas.edu.au
- 2. Dr Biplob Chowdhury, University of Tasmania (Lecturer) biplob.chowdhury@utas.edu.au
- 3. Mr Panut Suttinont, FSA, Muang Thai Life Assurance (Senior Assistant Vice President) panut_s@muangthai.co.th